// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "which road is amdt located?",
    answer: "galle road",
    options: [
      "mathara roadr",
      "galle road",
      "colombo",
      "hambantota"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "when was amdt found?",
    answer: "2005",
    options: [
      "2015",
      "2010",
      "2000",
      "2005"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "name one of the 4 colors in the amdt logo?",
    answer: "red,blue,yellow and green",
    options: [
      "red,blue,yellow and green",
      "red,white,yellow and green",
      "red,blue,yellow and black",
      "red,purple,yellow and green"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "what hastag does amdt use?",
    answer: "#weareamdt",
    options: [
      "#Sthy",
      "#Amdt",
      "#weeamdt",
      "#weareamdt"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "how many degree courses does amdt offer?",
    answer: "9 courses",
    options: [
      "12 courses",
      "4 courses",
      "9 courses",
      "5 courses"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "how many social media channels does amdt use?",
    answer: "4 social channels",
    options: [
      "4 social channels",
      "8 social channels",
      "12 social channels",
      "9 social channels"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "amdt is partnered with which university from the uk?",
    answer: "Falmouth university",
    options: [
      "kembridge",
      "nibm",
      "nsbm",
      "Falmouth university"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "how old is amdt now?",
    answer: "16",
    options: [
      "31",
      "18",
      "52",
      "16"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "what was the event that amdt did on january 26th of 2020?",
    answer: "premier league",
    options: [
      "exhibition",
      "ceremony",
      "party",
      "premier league"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "does amdt offer a foundation course?",
    answer: "yes",
    options: [
      "maybe",
      "not yet",
      "no",
      "yes"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];